> KIRSTEN ALLEN

kirsten@kallenillustration.com

Graphic Designer & Frontend Dev Austin, TX / Remote

Kirsten specializes in creating fun and interesting graphic solutions across many styles and platforms, with a detail-oriented mindset and a drive to experiment, iterate, and play.

> Skills

Graphic Design and Illustration

Frontend and UI Design

Animation and 3D

Brand and Identity

Print and Production

Apparel and Merchandising

> Specifics

Adobe Creative Suite

Blender

Version Control

HTML/CSS/JS

React

Various CMS Platforms

Various Ecommerce Platforms

Microsoft Office Suite

Google Office Suite

Mac & Windows Proficient

> See more

codepen.com/kirstenallen

github.com/kirstenallen

squarecarousel.com

savannahstagecompany.com

upliftdesk.com

kallenillustration.com

> Other

Sketching Woodworking Amateur 3D Modeler

> Work History

Uplift Desk Austin, TX 2020-2023

Graphic Designer

Responsible for weekly newsletters, sales, production assets for web and print. Additionally, created and implemented several features for the website to improve usability include homepage updates, support page updates, and a custom comparison chart feature.

GRAV Austin, TX 2016-2019

Graphic Designer

Created an original direct to consumer ecommerce website with B2C and B2B channels on the Shopify platform. Maintained and updated the site with new features as a one-person dev department, while contributing to asset creation and management for marketing.

T-Formation Tallahassee, FL 2014-2015

Graphic Designer

Worked to create and execute illustrations and designs for screen printing for large volume clients such as Nike, McDonalds, Geico and more, as well as maintaining meticulous records of samples and process materials.

> Education

SCAD Savannah, GA 2008 - 2012

Bachelor of Fine Arts Degree

Specialization in Graphic Design & Illustration